<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RGGP</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="there_are_some_pictures_of_our_college_which_is_taken_on_cultural_events">There are some pictures of our institute which is taken on Cultural Events.</string>
    <string name="college_staff">COLLEGE STAFF</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="head_of_departments">HEAD OF DEPARTMENTS</string>
    <string name="mr_sandeep_kumar_te">Mr. Sandeep Singh (TE)</string>
    <string name="student">Students</string>
    <string name="priyanka_choudhary_cse">Smt. Priyanka Choudhary (CSE)</string>
    <string name="radheshyam_bishnoi_ce">Mr. Radheshyam Bishnoi (CE)</string>
    <string name="mr_rahul_singla_ee">Mr. Rahul Singla (EE)</string>
    <string name="mr_anil_monga_me">Mr. Anil Monga (ME)</string>
    <string name="mr_sandeep_kumar_tt">Mr. Sandeep Singh (TT)</string>
    <string name="ayush_and_aaditya">Ayush And Aaditya</string>
    <string name="computer_engg">Branch : Computer Engg.</string>
    <string name="ayush_nain">Name : Ayush Nain</string>
    <string name="aaditya_kumar">Name : Aaditya Kumar</string>
    <string name="gpnarwana_ac_in">gpnarwana.ac.in</string>
    <string name="rggp">RGGP</string>
    <string name="rajiv_gandhi_govt_polytechnic_narwana">Rajiv Gandhi Govt. Polytechnic, Narwana</string>
    <string name="approved_by_aicte_new_delhi_amp_govt_of_haryana_affiliated_to_hsbte_panchkula"><![CDATA[(approved by aicte, new delhi & govt. of haryana, affiliated to hsbte panchkula.)]]></string>
    <string name="principle_message">principle message</string>
    <string name="it_s_an_immense_pleasure_to_welcome_you_all_to_rajiv_gandhi_govt_polytechnic_narwana_we_aim_to_provide_quality_technical_educationwith_great_emphasis_on_human_values_technical_professional_entrepreneurial_skills_for_sustainable_growth_of_society_and_nation_as_a_whole_we_believe_that_the_purpose_of_education_is_to_facillitate_the_development_of_clarity_of_aspirations_and_adequate_competence_to_actualize_it_since_its_establishment_in_2009_the_institute_has_made_its_presence_strongly_felt_in_the_technical_education_community_not_only_in_the_region_but_at_state_level_too_a_range_of_achievement_in_academics_in_all_six_branches_is_attained_by_joint_efforts_of_all_stake_holders_our_very_young_alumni_continue_to_keep_the_institute_name_high">It\'s an immense pleasure to welcome you all to Rajiv Gandhi Govt. Polytechnic, Narwana. We aim to provide quality technical educationwith great emphasis on human values, technical, professional, entrepreneurial skills for sustainable growth of society and nation as a whole. We believe that the purpose of education is to facillitate the development of clarity of aspirations and adequate competence to actualize it. Since its establishment in 2009, the institute has made its presence strongly felt in the technical education community not only in the region but at state level too. A range of achievement in academics in all six branches is attained by joint efforts of all stake holders. Our very young alumni continue to keep the institute name high.</string>
    <string name="this_institute_is_well_equipped_with_laboratory_workshop_rich_collectionof_book_resources_in_library_computing_facility_internet_facilityand_industry_institute_interaction_facilities_which_enriches_the_process_of_learning_our_teaching_learning_process_is_based_on_practical_inclusive_and_motivational_approach_in_addition_to_excellent_teaching_the_faculty_members_are_actively_involved_in_over_all_training_and_placement_activities_of_the_students_and_monitoring_them_about_their_carrier_path_and_overall_development_our_faculty_is_also_actively_attending_participating_seminar_workshops_training_conferencing_conducted_by_nitttr_aicte_and_other_eminent_institute_time_to_time_enrich_their_knowledge_and_to_update_with_latest_technology_with_the_guidance_of_seniors_supports_from_colleagues_and_decoration_of_diligent_workforce_i_wish_and_hope_this_premier_institute_to_scale_higher_heights"><![CDATA[This institute is well equipped with laboratory, workshop, rich collectionof book/resources in library, computing facility, internet facilityand industry-institute interaction facilities which enriches the process of learning. Our teaching learning process is based on practical, inclusive and motivational approach. In addition to excellent teaching, the faculty members are actively involved in over all training and placement activities of the students and monitoring them about their carrier path and overall development. Our faculty is also actively attending & participating seminar/workshops/training & conferencing conducted by NITTTR/AICTE and other eminent Institute time to time enrich their knowledge and to update with latest technology. With the guidance of seniors, supports from colleagues and decoration of diligent workforce, I wish and hope this premier institute to scale higher heights.]]></string>
    <string name="thank_you">Thank you</string>
    <string name="with_warm_regard">With warm regard</string>
    <string name="mr_jaswant_singh">Mr. Jaswant Singh</string>
    <string name="principal">Principal</string>
    <string name="our_mission">Our Mission</string>
    <string name="_1_to_excel_student_centred_learning_environment">1. To excel student centred learning environment.</string>
    <string name="_2_to_develop_professional_skills_through_industry_academic_interface">2. To develop professional skills through Industry academic interface.</string>
    <string name="_3_to_enhance_the_teaching_learning_process_through_digital_technologies">3. To enhance the teaching learning process through digital technologies.</string>
    <string name="_4_to_inculcate_ethical_values_entrepreneurial_skills_and_teamwork_spirit">4. To inculcate ethical values, entrepreneurial skills and teamwork spirit.</string>
    <string name="our_values">Our Values</string>
    <string name="to_transform_younger_minds_into_valuable_resources_with_technical_professional_and_entrepreneurial_skills_for_sustainable_growth_of_society_and_nation_as_a_whole">To transform younger minds into valuable resources with technical, professional and entrepreneurial skills for sustainable growth of society and Nation as a whole.</string>
    <string name="our_missio">Our Mission</string>
    <string name="our_vision">Our Vision</string>
    <string name="one_of_the_most_crucial_elements_in_out_lives_is_self_comfidence_without_it_we_may_find_it_difficult_to_achieve_anything_it_s_vital_not_to_lose_our_self_confidence_when_facing_challenges_or_tough_times_everyone_goes_through_them_managing_our_time_wisely_is_also_important_maintainig_a_good_character_is_essential_regardless_of_our_action_moving_forward_with_this_mindset_is_key_we_should_believe_that_nothing_is_impossible_this_belief_empowers_us_to_tackle_challenging_tasks_effortlessly_life_is_a_precious_gift_and_we_should_cheris_it_going_forward_with_a_good_character_and_a_positive_attitude_is_essential_even_in_challenging_times_staying_positive_is_crucial_remember_a_positive_attitude_is_the_most_potent_tool_for_achieving_success_in_life">One of the most crucial elements in out lives is self-comfidence. Without it, we may find it difficult to achieve anything. It\'s vital not to lose our self-confidence when facing challenges or tough times; everyone goes through them. Managing our time wisely is also important. Maintainig a good character is essential, regardless of our action. Moving forward with this mindset is key. We should believe that nothing is impossible; this belief empowers us to tackle challenging tasks effortlessly. Life is a precious gift, and we should cheris it. Going forward with a good character and a positive attitude is essential. Even in challenging times, staying positive is crucial. Remember a positive attitude is the most potent tool for achieving success in life.</string>
    <string name="queries_for_admissions_please_contact">Queries For Admissions Please Contact</string>
    <string name="_91_92156_20009">(+91-92156-20009)</string>
    <string name="dedication_to_education_is_our_strength">Dedication to Education is Our Strength.</string>
    <string name="courses">Courses</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="our_courses">Our Courses</string>
    <string name="civil_engineering">Civil Engineering</string>
    <string name="computer_engineering">Computer Engineering</string>
    <string name="electrical_engineering">Electrical Engineering</string>
    <string name="mechanical_engineering">Mechanical Engineering</string>
    <string name="textile_design">Textile Design</string>
    <string name="textile_process">Textile Processing</string>
    <string name="textile_chem">Textile Chemistry</string>
    <string name="textile_technology">Textile Technology</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="rajiv_gandhi_govt_polytechnic_narwana_was_established_in_2007_with_the_aim_to_enhance_employbility_of_the_youth_by_equipping_them_with_latest_technical_skills_for_suitable_at_the_main_national_highway_nh_71_at_patiala_road_with_acquiring_area_of_10_11_acres_near_iti_campus_the_campus_is_laid_out_with_ambient_lush_green_infrastructure_teaching_block_sports_ground_and_fully_wi_fi_campus_the_institute_has_spacious_and_well_ventialated_class_rooms_labs_equipped_with_latest_and_modern_machinery_to_impact_practical_knowledge_to_the_students_and_well_stocked_library_and_e_library">Rajiv Gandhi Govt. Polytechnic, Narwana was established in 2007 with the aim to enhance employbility of the youth by equipping them with latest technical skills for suitable at the main National Highway NH-71 at Patiala Road with Acquiring area of 10.11 acres near ITI campus. The Campus is laid out with Ambient lush green infrastructure, teaching block, Sports ground and fully Wi-Fi Campus. The Institute has spacious and well ventialated class rooms, labs equipped with latest and modern machinery to impact practical knowledge to the students and well stocked library and E-library.</string>
    <string name="the_institute_started_as_a_center_of_excellence_in_textiles_running_with_textile_technology_branch_with_intake_of_60_seats_guest_class_has_started_at_govt_polytechnic_hisar_from_the_session_2007_08_the_classes_are_running_in_its_own_campus_from_academic_session_2009_10_with_three_textile_branches_with_an_intake_of_60_seats">The Institute started as a center of excellence in Textiles, running with Textile Technology branch with intake of 60 seats(guest class has started at Govt. Polytechnic, Hisar) from the session 2007-08. The classes are running in its own Campus from academic session 2009-10 with three Textile branches with an intake of 60 seats at mentioned below:-</string>
    <string name="s_no">S. No.</string>
    <string name="course">Course</string>
    <string name="dur">Duration</string>
    <string name="yos">Year Of Start</string>
    <string name="intake">Intake For Session 2009–10</string>
    <string name="_1">1.</string>
    <string name="_2">2.</string>
    <string name="_3">3.</string>
    <string name="_3_years">3 Years</string>
    <string name="_2007_08">2007-08</string>
    <string name="_2009_10">2009-10</string>
    <string name="_60">60</string>
    <string name="_120">120</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="_180">180</string>
    <string name="from_the_session_2010_11_one_new_diploma_course_textile_design_has_been_introduced_in_place_of_textile_processing_with_the_intake_of_120_seats_in_each_branch">from the session 2010-11 one new diploma course Textile Design has been introduced in place of Textile processing with the intake of 120 seats in each branch.</string>
    <string name="_360">360</string>
    <string name="_2010_11">2010-11</string>
    <string name="now_at_the_present_academic_session_2011_12_five_new_diploma_courses_have_been_introduced_with_the_total_intake_of_540_in_the_institute_the_detailed_of_branches_intake_are_given_below">Now at the present academic session 2011-12, five new diploma courses have been introduced with the total intake of 540 in the Institute. The detailed of Branches/intake are given below:-</string>
    <string name="_4">4.</string>
    <string name="mechanical_engg">Mechanical Engg.</string>
    <string name="_2011_12">2011-12</string>
    <string name="_5">5.</string>
    <string name="civil_engg">Civil Engg.</string>
    <string name="_6">6.</string>
    <string name="electrical_engg">Electrical Engg.</string>
    <string name="_7">7.</string>
    <string name="garments_technology">Garments Technology</string>
    <string name="_8">8.</string>
    <string name="knitting_technology">Knitting Technology</string>
    <string name="_540">540</string>
    <string name="institute_running_6_diploma_courses_with_approximately_1000_students_on_roll_under_the_guidance_of_matured_dedicated_experienced_and_highly_qualified_staff">Institute running 6 Diploma courses with approximately 1000 students on roll under the guidance of matured, dedicated, experienced and highly qualified staff.</string>
    <string name="above_six_engineering_courses_are_running_till_date_with_the_same_intake">Above Six Engineering Courses are running till date with the same intake.</string>
    <string name="computer_enggi">Computer Engg.</string>
    <string name="comp_article1">Computer engineering is a dynamic discipline that integrates principles of electrical engineering and computer science to design, develop, and maintain computer systems and hardware. It focuses on creating innovative solutions for complex computing challenges, ranging from microprocessors and embedded systems to high-performance computing and artificial intelligence applications.</string>
    <string name="comp_article2">Computer engineers design hardware components such as processors, circuit boards, and memory systems while also working on software development, including operating systems and firmware. They play a vital role in optimizing the interaction between hardware and software, ensuring systems perform efficiently and reliably. </string>

    <string name="our_teachers">Our Teachers</string>
    <string name="comp_article3">This field underpins technological advancements in diverse industries, including healthcare, automotive, telecommunications, and robotics. Computer engineers also address emerging challenges such as cybersecurity, sustainable computing, and machine learning integration. With its blend of technical expertise and creative problem-solving, computer engineering drives innovation, shaping the future of technology and its impact on society.</string>
    <string name="teachers">Teachers are the foundation of education and play an essential role in nurturing the intellectual, emotional, and social development of students. They are more than educators—they are mentors, guides, and role models who inspire and influence young minds to achieve their full potential. We have following teachers:</string>
    <string name="_1_smt_priyanka_choudhary_hod">1. Smt. Priyanka Choudhary (HOD)</string>
    <string name="_1_mr_radheshyam">1. Mr. Radheshyam Bishnoi (HOD)</string>
    <string name="_1_mr_rahul">1. Mr. Rahul Singla (HOD)</string>
    <string name="_2_mr_jitendra_mor">2. Mr. Jitendra Mor</string>
    <string name="_3_mr_ajay_malik">3. Mr. Ajay Malik</string>
    <string name="_4_mr_arun">4. Mr. Arun Sharma</string>
    <string name="elect1">Electrical engineering is a versatile and impactful field focused on the study, design, and application of systems and devices powered by electricity, electronics, and electromagnetism. It encompasses a wide range of areas, including power generation and distribution, communication systems, electronics, control systems, and renewable energy technologies.

</string>
    <string name="elec2">This discipline combines theoretical knowledge with practical problem-solving to create systems that improve everyday life, from household appliances to complex industrial machinery. Electrical engineers are key contributors to technological progress, ensuring that electrical systems are reliable, efficient, and safe. Their expertise drives advancements in sectors like healthcare, transportation, telecommunications, and renewable energy.</string>
    <string name="elec3">Electrical engineers design and develop critical infrastructure such as power grids, motors, and circuits, as well as advanced technologies like semiconductors, robotics, and wireless communication systems. They play a pivotal role in innovating energy-efficient solutions and addressing global challenges, such as sustainable energy and smart technology integration.</string>
    <string name="_2_ravi_kalra">2. Mr. Ravi Kalra</string>
    <string name="_3_sanpreet_kaur">3. Ms. Sunpreet Kaur</string>
    <string name="_4_alka_kalra">4. Mrs. Alka Kalra</string>
    <string name="_5_mr_sandeep_kumar">5. Mr. Sandeep Kumar</string>
    <string name="civil_engineering_is_a_cornerstone_of_modern_infrastructure_focusing_on_the_design_construction_and_maintenance_of_essential_structures_and_systems_that_support_society_this_versatile_discipline_encompasses_various_specialties_including_structural_engineering_transportation_geotechnical_engineering_environmental_engineering_and_urban_planning">Civil engineering is a cornerstone of modern infrastructure, focusing on the design, construction, and maintenance of essential structures and systems that support society. This versatile discipline encompasses various specialties, including structural engineering, transportation, geotechnical engineering, environmental engineering, and urban planning.</string>
    <string name="civil_engineers_design_and_build_roads_bridges_dams_buildings_water_treatment_systems_and_other_critical_infrastructure_they_ensure_these_structures_are_safe_sustainable_and_efficient_taking_into_account_factors_such_as_materials_environmental_impact_and_cost_their_work_often_involves_solving_complex_challenges_such_as_earthquake_resistant_designs_or_innovative_flood_control_systems">Civil engineers design and build roads, bridges, dams, buildings, water treatment systems, and other critical infrastructure. They ensure these structures are safe, sustainable, and efficient, taking into account factors such as materials, environmental impact, and cost. Their work often involves solving complex challenges, such as earthquake-resistant designs or innovative flood control systems.</string>
    <string name="with_a_blend_of_creativity_technical_expertise_and_problem_solving_skills_civil_engineers_play_a_vital_role_in_shaping_the_physical_environment_and_addressing_global_challenges_like_urbanization_climate_change_and_resource_management_their_contributions_enhance_quality_of_life_promote_economic_growth_and_ensure_a_sustainable_future_for_communities_worldwide">With a blend of creativity, technical expertise, and problem-solving skills, civil engineers play a vital role in shaping the physical environment and addressing global challenges like urbanization, climate change, and resource management. Their contributions enhance quality of life, promote economic growth, and ensure a sustainable future for communities worldwide.</string>
    <string name="_2_smt_manju">2. Smt. Manju</string>
    <string name="_3_mr_surender">3. Mr. Surender</string>
    <string name="_4_mr_parveen_kumar">4. Mr. Parveen Kumar</string>
    <string name="mechanical_engineering_is_a_broad_and_dynamic_discipline_that_applies_principles_of_physics_mathematics_and_material_science_to_design_analyze_manufacture_and_maintain_mechanical_systems_it_is_one_of_the_oldest_and_most_versatile_branches_of_engineering_driving_innovation_in_industries_ranging_from_automotive_and_aerospace_to_energy_robotics_and_healthcare">Mechanical engineering is a broad and dynamic discipline that applies principles of physics, mathematics, and material science to design, analyze, manufacture, and maintain mechanical systems. It is one of the oldest and most versatile branches of engineering, driving innovation in industries ranging from automotive and aerospace to energy, robotics, and healthcare.</string>
    <string name="mechanical_engineers_work_on_a_wide_array_of_projects_including_developing_engines_machines_tools_and_thermal_systems_they_leverage_advanced_technologies_such_as_computer_aided_design_cad_simulation_and_automation_to_create_efficient_and_sustainable_solutions_the_field_also_encompasses_emerging_areas_like_nanotechnology_renewable_energy_systems_and_smart_materials">Mechanical engineers work on a wide array of projects, including developing engines, machines, tools, and thermal systems. They leverage advanced technologies such as computer-aided design (CAD), simulation, and automation to create efficient and sustainable solutions. The field also encompasses emerging areas like nanotechnology, renewable energy systems, and smart materials.</string>
    <string name="with_a_focus_on_problem_solving_and_innovation_mechanical_engineering_addresses_real_world_challenges_such_as_energy_efficiency_environmental_sustainability_and_technological_advancement_mechanical_engineers_play_a_vital_role_in_improving_the_quality_of_life_contributing_to_the_design_and_production_of_systems_that_power_move_and_sustain_the_modern_world">With a focus on problem-solving and innovation, mechanical engineering addresses real-world challenges, such as energy efficiency, environmental sustainability, and technological advancement. Mechanical engineers play a vital role in improving the quality of life, contributing to the design and production of systems that power, move, and sustain the modern world.</string>
    <string name="_1_mr_anil_monga_hod">1. Mr. Anil Monga (HOD)</string>
    <string name="_2_mr_jaswant_singh">2. Mr. Jaswant Singh</string>
    <string name="_3_mr_vinod_kumar">3. Mr. Vinod Kumar</string>
    <string name="_4_mr_mohinderpal">4. Mr. Mohinderpal</string>
    <string name="textile_engineering">Textile Engineering</string>
    <string name="textile_engineering_is_a_specialized_field_that_combines_principles_of_engineering_chemistry_and_material_science_to_design_develop_and_optimize_textile_products_and_manufacturing_processes_it_focuses_on_the_creation_of_fibers_fabrics_and_garments_as_well_as_advanced_textile_applications_in_industries_like_automotive_healthcare_and_aerospace">Textile engineering is a specialized field that combines principles of engineering, chemistry, and material science to design, develop, and optimize textile products and manufacturing processes. It focuses on the creation of fibers, fabrics, and garments, as well as advanced textile applications in industries like automotive, healthcare, and aerospace.</string>
    <string name="textile_engineers_work_with_natural_and_synthetic_fibers_to_develop_materials_with_desired_properties_such_as_durability_elasticity_and_thermal_resistance_they_also_innovate_in_areas_like_smart_textiles_which_integrate_electronics_and_sensors_and_sustainable_textiles_which_use_eco_friendly_materials_and_processes_to_reduce_environmental_impact">Textile engineers work with natural and synthetic fibers to develop materials with desired properties, such as durability, elasticity, and thermal resistance. They also innovate in areas like smart textiles, which integrate electronics and sensors, and sustainable textiles, which use eco-friendly materials and processes to reduce environmental impact.</string>
    <string name="this_field_encompasses_various_aspects_including_yarn_production_fabric_weaving_and_knitting_dyeing_finishing_and_quality_control_textile_engineers_play_a_crucial_role_in_advancing_technology_for_functional_clothing_protective_gear_and_technical_fabrics_their_work_enhances_everyday_products_and_drives_innovation_across_industries_making_textiles_both_practical_and_cutting_edge">This field encompasses various aspects, including yarn production, fabric weaving and knitting, dyeing, finishing, and quality control. Textile engineers play a crucial role in advancing technology for functional clothing, protective gear, and technical fabrics. Their work enhances everyday products and drives innovation across industries, making textiles both practical and cutting-edge.</string>
    <string name="_1_mr_sunil_sheoran">1. Mr. Sunil Sheoran</string>
    <string name="_2_mr_rajesh_saini">2. Mr. Rajesh Saini</string>
    <string name="_3_ranbir_kundu">3. Ranbir Kundu</string>
    <string name="_4_mr_jagbir">4. Mr. Jagbir</string>

</resources>